{"Questions": [{"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "What is the \u201cGreen Revolution\"?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n A period of research and development that increased agricultural output \n", "\n A period of research to find new ways to sell agricultural products\n", "\n A period of research to get rid of poverty\n", "\n A period of research to find ways to no longer harm the environment\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "The catalyst that started the Spanish-American War was the:\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n explosion of a military building in Cuba\n", "\n the explosion and sinking of the USS Maine \n", "\n the assassination of an important Spanish leader\n", "\n yellow journalism\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "2", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Racism is best shown at the Paris World's Fair through the use of:\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n European \u201craces\u201d in Human Zoo exhibits\n", "\n The fact that the French did not allow people from Russia into the Gallery of Machines\n", "\n Members of French colonies in the Human Zoos \n", "\n The fact that the French did not invite the Germans to the World's Fair\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "The definition of Trench Warfare would be:\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Militias attack and defend from a set of trenches, and move large distances in short periods of time\n", "\n Opposing armed forces attack and defend from relatively permanent system of trenches \n", "\n Opposing armed forces attack and defend from a single trench on either side that is split by no-man\u2019s land\n", "\n Militaries only use massive amounts of infantry in the trenches to fight each other, without any use of artillery\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "3", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "All of the following are reasons why the Treaty of Versailles embarrassed Germany except:\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The German leaders were not invited to the peace negotiations\n", "\n Germany was forced to pay for all the damages during WWI\n", "\n The German empire was split up and virtually destroyed\n", "\n Versailles made Germany a puppet government for the French \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following document to answer the question.\n\t\u201cSome kind of idea is at the beginning of every political movement. It is not necessary to put this idea in a thick book, nor that it take political form in a hundred long paragraphs. History proves that the greatest world movements have always developed when their leaders knew how to unify their followers under a short, clear theme. That is clear from the French Revolution, or Cromwell's movement, or Buddhism, Islam, or Christianity. Christ's goal was clear and simple: \u201cLove your neighbor as yourself.\u201d He gathered his followers behind that straightforward statement. Because this teaching was simple, crisp, clear, and understandable, enabling the broad masses to stand behind it, it in the end conquered the world.\n\tOne then builds a whole system of thought on such a brief, crisply formulated idea. The idea does not remain limited to this single statement, rather it is applied to every aspect of daily life and becomes the guide for all human activity \u2014 politics, culture, the economy, every area of human behavior. It becomes a worldview. We see that in all great revolutionary movements, which begin with a clear, crisp, understandable, all-encompassing idea. They spread more and more and become a mirror of life that reflects all activities of the peoples, and indeed in a particular way.\"\n\nSource: Joseph Goebbels, Chief Propaganda Officer for the Nazi Party, Speech, 1928\n\nWhat is the most likely reason Goebbels invokes religion in the first paragraph?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Most Germans are Christian, and would therefore easily relate \n", "\n Goebbels hates Christianity and wants to make it appear mischievous\n", "\n Goebbels and the rest of the Nazis value Christian loyalty above all else\n", "\n Christianity is at the core of Nazi ideology\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following document to answer the question.\n\t\u201cSome kind of idea is at the beginning of every political movement. It is not necessary to put this idea in a thick book, nor that it take political form in a hundred long paragraphs. History proves that the greatest world movements have always developed when their leaders knew how to unify their followers under a short, clear theme. That is clear from the French Revolution, or Cromwell's movement, or Buddhism, Islam, or Christianity. Christ's goal was clear and simple: \u201cLove your neighbor as yourself.\u201d He gathered his followers behind that straightforward statement. Because this teaching was simple, crisp, clear, and understandable, enabling the broad masses to stand behind it, it in the end conquered the world.\n\tOne then builds a whole system of thought on such a brief, crisply formulated idea. The idea does not remain limited to this single statement, rather it is applied to every aspect of daily life and becomes the guide for all human activity \u2014 politics, culture, the economy, every area of human behavior. It becomes a worldview. We see that in all great revolutionary movements, which begin with a clear, crisp, understandable, all-encompassing idea. They spread more and more and become a mirror of life that reflects all activities of the peoples, and indeed in a particular way.\"\n\nSource: Joseph Goebbels, Chief Propaganda Officer for the Nazi Party, Speech, 1928\n\nWhat is the immediate historical context of this source?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The Nazi party had recently been elected, and Goebbels is discussing the success of campaigning\n", "\n The Nazis had not won an election by 1928, but they were starting to adjust their party platform \n", "\n Hitler had lost control of the party, and Goebbels had taken over\n", "\n Hitler had just been imprisoned, and Goebbels was temporarily in charge\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following document to answer the question.\n\t\u201cSome kind of idea is at the beginning of every political movement. It is not necessary to put this idea in a thick book, nor that it take political form in a hundred long paragraphs. History proves that the greatest world movements have always developed when their leaders knew how to unify their followers under a short, clear theme. That is clear from the French Revolution, or Cromwell's movement, or Buddhism, Islam, or Christianity. Christ's goal was clear and simple: \u201cLove your neighbor as yourself.\u201d He gathered his followers behind that straightforward statement. Because this teaching was simple, crisp, clear, and understandable, enabling the broad masses to stand behind it, it in the end conquered the world.\n\tOne then builds a whole system of thought on such a brief, crisply formulated idea. The idea does not remain limited to this single statement, rather it is applied to every aspect of daily life and becomes the guide for all human activity \u2014 politics, culture, the economy, every area of human behavior. It becomes a worldview. We see that in all great revolutionary movements, which begin with a clear, crisp, understandable, all-encompassing idea. They spread more and more and become a mirror of life that reflects all activities of the peoples, and indeed in a particular way.\"\n\nSource: Joseph Goebbels, Chief Propaganda Officer for the Nazi Party, Speech, 1928\n\nWhich of the following options is the best summary of the argument in the source?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Propaganda is at the core of all important political movements\n", "\n Party messages should be simple and clear so everyone can understand them \n", "\n Political parties should invoke religion in order to successfully deliver a point\n", "\n Germany deserves a strong, centralized party such as the Nazis.\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "2", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following passage to answer the question. \nFirst, let us consider the inner man to see how a righteous, free, and pious Christian, that is, a spiritual, new, and inner man, becomes what he is. It is evident that no external thing has any influence in producing Christian righteousness or freedom, or in producing unrighteousness or servitude. A simple argument will furnish the proof of this statement. What can it profit the soul if the body is well, free, and active, and eats, drinks, and does as it pleases? For in these respects even the most godless slaves of vice may prosper. On the other hand, how will poor health or imprisonment or hunger or thirst or any other external misfortune harm the soul? Even the most godly men, and those who are free because of clear consciences, are afflicted with these things. None of these things touch either the freedom or the servitude of the soul. It does not help the soul if the body is adorned with the sacred robes of priests or dwells in sacred places or is occupied with sacred duties or prays, fasts, abstains from certain kinds of food, or does any work that can be done by the body and in the body. The righteousness and the freedom of the soul require something far different since the things which have been mentioned could be done by any wicked person. Such works produce nothing but hypocrites. On the other hand, it will not harm the soul if the body is clothed in secular dress, dwells in unconsecrated places, eats and drinks as others do, does not pray aloud, and neglects to do all the above-mentioned things which hypocrites can do.\n\nSource: Martin Luther, On Christian Liberty (1521), pg 25.\n\nThe passage above best describes which recurring topic of religious faiths in world history?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The competition between the power of the leaders of the faith and political leaders\n", "\n The apocalyptic nature of monotheistic religions in the Early Modern Era\n", "\n The idea of separating the physical body from the spiritual soul \n", "\n The use of physical imagery in religious argumentation\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following passage to answer the question. \nFirst, let us consider the inner man to see how a righteous, free, and pious Christian, that is, a spiritual, new, and inner man, becomes what he is. It is evident that no external thing has any influence in producing Christian righteousness or freedom, or in producing unrighteousness or servitude. A simple argument will furnish the proof of this statement. What can it profit the soul if the body is well, free, and active, and eats, drinks, and does as it pleases? For in these respects even the most godless slaves of vice may prosper. On the other hand, how will poor health or imprisonment or hunger or thirst or any other external misfortune harm the soul? Even the most godly men, and those who are free because of clear consciences, are afflicted with these things. None of these things touch either the freedom or the servitude of the soul. It does not help the soul if the body is adorned with the sacred robes of priests or dwells in sacred places or is occupied with sacred duties or prays, fasts, abstains from certain kinds of food, or does any work that can be done by the body and in the body. The righteousness and the freedom of the soul require something far different since the things which have been mentioned could be done by any wicked person. Such works produce nothing but hypocrites. On the other hand, it will not harm the soul if the body is clothed in secular dress, dwells in unconsecrated places, eats and drinks as others do, does not pray aloud, and neglects to do all the above-mentioned things which hypocrites can do.\n\nSource: Martin Luther, On Christian Liberty (1521), pg 25.\n\nWhich of the following best describes Luther's argument from the passage above? \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Nothing physical can affect a person's spirit, therefore good deeds are not needed in life\n", "\n No good work can guarantee entrance to heaven, just as no physical harm can harm the inner man \n", "\n Special dress and deeds can help a Christian gain entrance to heaven\n", "\n Hypocrites and wicked people can gain entrance to heaven just like everyone else\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following passage to answer the question. \nFirst, let us consider the inner man to see how a righteous, free, and pious Christian, that is, a spiritual, new, and inner man, becomes what he is. It is evident that no external thing has any influence in producing Christian righteousness or freedom, or in producing unrighteousness or servitude. A simple argument will furnish the proof of this statement. What can it profit the soul if the body is well, free, and active, and eats, drinks, and does as it pleases? For in these respects even the most godless slaves of vice may prosper. On the other hand, how will poor health or imprisonment or hunger or thirst or any other external misfortune harm the soul? Even the most godly men, and those who are free because of clear consciences, are afflicted with these things. None of these things touch either the freedom or the servitude of the soul. It does not help the soul if the body is adorned with the sacred robes of priests or dwells in sacred places or is occupied with sacred duties or prays, fasts, abstains from certain kinds of food, or does any work that can be done by the body and in the body. The righteousness and the freedom of the soul require something far different since the things which have been mentioned could be done by any wicked person. Such works produce nothing but hypocrites. On the other hand, it will not harm the soul if the body is clothed in secular dress, dwells in unconsecrated places, eats and drinks as others do, does not pray aloud, and neglects to do all the above-mentioned things which hypocrites can do.\n\nSource: Martin Luther, On Christian Liberty (1521), pg 25.\n\nWhich piece of historical context best describes Luther's arguments in the passage above as well as his other arguments of the Protestant Reformation?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The Catholic Church had a surge of popularity in Europe during the later Middle Ages \n", "\n Many people in Europe in the Middle Ages began to feel disenfranchised from and distrusting of the Catholic Church \n", "\n The Renaissance encouraged a questioning of church authority from lay Christians\n", "\n The Thirty Years' War encouraged massive resistance to the Catholic Church\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Which of the following is in the correct historical order?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The Seven Years' War, The French Revolution, The Haitian Revolution, The Opium War \n", "\n The Haitian Revolution, The American Revolution, The Opium War, The Sepoy Rebellion\n", "\n The Latin American Revolution, The Haitian Revolution, The Franco-Prussian War, The collapse of the Holy Roman Empire\n", "\n The Opium War, The American Revolution, The Haitian Revolution, The Latin American Revolutions\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "What term is used to describe the \"scientific process of attempting to keep certain genes through encouraging reproduction while attempting to remove unwanted genes through discouraging reproduction\"?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Social Darwinism\n", "\n Eugenics \n", "\n Natural Selection\n", "\n Nationalism\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "2", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "All of the following are ways education in the colonies promoted colonization except:\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Education in the colonies promoted European history and European culture\n", "\n Education in the colonies focused on developing basic skills of reading, writing, and arithmetic, but did not develop serious critical thinking skills\n", "\n Education in the colonies focused on developing religious knowledge and literacy, but only taught enough for low-level positions ??? Double check\n", "\n Education in the colonies used European structured schools to teach native students European history, European politics, and traditional languages\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "3", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "All of the following could be considered \"Enlightenment documents\" except:\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The Declaration of Independence\n", "\n The Jamaica Letter\n", "\n The Declaration of Rights of Man and Citizen\n", "\n The Communist Manifesto \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Why were the British eager to create a colonial relationship with the khedivate in Egypt in the mid- 1800s?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n In order to weaken the French holdings in North Africa\n", "\n In order to gain access to the Suez Canal \n", "\n In order to help their ally, the Ottoman Empire\n", "\n In order to control the Persian Gulf\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "3", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following source to answer the question.\n\"Modern industry has converted the little workshop of the patriarchal master into the great factory of the industrial capitalist. Masses of laborers, crowded into the factory, are organized like soldiers. As privates of the industrial army they are placed under the command of a perfect hierarchy of officers and sergeants. Not only are they slaves of the bourgeois class, and of the bourgeois state; they are daily and hourly enslaved by the machine, by the overlooker, and, above all, by the individual bourgeois manufacturer himself. The more openly this despotism proclaims gain to be its end and aim, the more petty, the more hateful and the more embittering it is.\nThe less the skill and exertion of strength implied in manual labor, in other words, the more modern industry becomes developed, the more it is labor of men superseded by that of women. Differences of age and sex have no longer any distinctive social validity for the working class. All are instruments of labor, more or less expensive to use, according to their age and sex.\nNo sooner is the exploitation of the laborer by the manufacturer, so far at an end, that he receives his wages in cash, than he is set upon by the other portions of the. Bourgeois, the landlord, the shopkeeper, the pawnbroker, etc.\"\n\nSource: Marx, Karl. The Communist Manifesto (1848)\n\nAll of the following are discussed in the first paragraph of the excerpt except:\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The transition from cottage industry to factory production\n", "\n Organization of labor in factories\n", "\n Comparisons between factory labor and military instruction\n", "\n The deterioration of the power of the bourgeois \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following source to answer the question.\n\"Modern industry has converted the little workshop of the patriarchal master into the great factory of the industrial capitalist. Masses of laborers, crowded into the factory, are organized like soldiers. As privates of the industrial army they are placed under the command of a perfect hierarchy of officers and sergeants. Not only are they slaves of the bourgeois class, and of the bourgeois state; they are daily and hourly enslaved by the machine, by the overlooker, and, above all, by the individual bourgeois manufacturer himself. The more openly this despotism proclaims gain to be its end and aim, the more petty, the more hateful and the more embittering it is.\nThe less the skill and exertion of strength implied in manual labor, in other words, the more modern industry becomes developed, the more it is labor of men superseded by that of women. Differences of age and sex have no longer any distinctive social validity for the working class. All are instruments of labor, more or less expensive to use, according to their age and sex.\nNo sooner is the exploitation of the laborer by the manufacturer, so far at an end, that he receives his wages in cash, than he is set upon by the other portions of the. Bourgeois, the landlord, the shopkeeper, the pawnbroker, etc.\"\n\nSource: Marx, Karl. The Communist Manifesto (1848)\n\nWhat is the main point of the second paragraph?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Industrial work can only be done by men\n", "\n Industrial work can be done by anyone \n", "\n Women's equality started in the factories\n", "\n Child labor laws are inspired by Marx\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "2", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following source to answer the question.\n\"Modern industry has converted the little workshop of the patriarchal master into the great factory of the industrial capitalist. Masses of laborers, crowded into the factory, are organized like soldiers. As privates of the industrial army they are placed under the command of a perfect hierarchy of officers and sergeants. Not only are they slaves of the bourgeois class, and of the bourgeois state; they are daily and hourly enslaved by the machine, by the overlooker, and, above all, by the individual bourgeois manufacturer himself. The more openly this despotism proclaims gain to be its end and aim, the more petty, the more hateful and the more embittering it is.\nThe less the skill and exertion of strength implied in manual labor, in other words, the more modern industry becomes developed, the more it is labor of men superseded by that of women. Differences of age and sex have no longer any distinctive social validity for the working class. All are instruments of labor, more or less expensive to use, according to their age and sex.\nNo sooner is the exploitation of the laborer by the manufacturer, so far at an end, that he receives his wages in cash, than he is set upon by the other portions of the. Bourgeois, the landlord, the shopkeeper, the pawnbroker, etc.\"\n\nSource: Marx, Karl. The Communist Manifesto (1848)\n\nWhat other forms of oppression do the industrial working class face outside the factory?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The working classes only face oppression in the factory\n", "\n The working classes face oppression through paying rent to landlords\n", "\n The working classes face oppression in many areas outside the factory, wherever the bourgeois are present \n", "\n The working classes face oppression in their homes due to social constraints of marriage and raising a family\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "3", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Which of the following events were not part of the modern era (1750-1900}?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The Haitian Revolution\n", "\n The Industrial Revolution\n", "\n The Berlin Conference\n", "\n World War One \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "A ________________ is an agricultural product that has very high commercial value and is grown for profits.\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n cash crop \n", "\n staple crop\n", "\n luxury crop\n", "\n mercantile crop\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "The Spanish brought this good from modern day Peru to China and Europe. It brought large amounts of wealth to the Spanish in the short run, but it helped lead them to financial ruin in the long run.\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Silver \n", "\n Gold\n", "\n Cotton\n", "\n Tobacco\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "What was the name of the monumental structure commissioned by the Pope Leo X in order to incorporate the ideas of the Renaissance with the Catholic Church?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n St. Peter\u2019s Basilica \n", "\n St. Paul\u2019s Cathedral\n", "\n The Great Orthodox Church\n", "\n The Eiffel Tower\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Martin Luther\u2019s challenge to the Catholic Church in 1517, as can be seen through the 95 Theses, was concerned with\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The sale of indulgences \n", "\n The pope\u2019s war with Venice\n", "\n The Holy Roman Emperor\u2019s use of Renaissance art\n", "\n The corruption of the Augustinian order\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Many Christians in late medieval and early modern Europe paid for indulgences to escape time in\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n purgatory \n", "\n hell\n", "\n prison\n", "\n the river Styx\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Mughal tax collectors were known as __________, while their estates were known as _____________.\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Zamindar, Zamindari \n", "\n Zamindari, Mulattos\n", "\n Zamindari, Zamindar\n", "\n Peninsulares, Criollos\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "The most successful Islamic Empire in India was the\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Mughal Empire \n", "\n Ottoman Empire\n", "\n Maurya Empire\n", "\n Delhi Sultanate\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "These were the highest class in Encomienda System\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Peninsulares \n", "\n Mestizos\n", "\n Mulattos\n", "\n Criollos\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": " All of the following are examples of how the Ming dynasty tried to reinstitute Chinese culture beginning in 1368 except\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Promoted trade with India \n", "\n Rid itself of Mongol legacies\n", "\n Promoted Confucian learning principles\n", "\n Promoted major works of history and art\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "What was the name of the treaty between Spain and Portugal concerning the Age of Exploration and the New World?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Treaty of Tordesillas \n", "\n Treaty of Lisbon\n", "\n Treaty of Portugal\n", "\n Treaty of Rome\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Which part of the New World ended up importing the largest number of African slaves by the year 1800?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Brazil \n", "\n The Caribbean\n", "\n The Thirteen Colonies\n", "\n Mexico\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "The best description of the Columbian Exchange is\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n the transfer of peoples, animals, plants, and diseases between the New and Old Worlds \n", "\n the transfer of goods between North America, Europe, and China\n", "\n the establishment and growth of the slave trade across the Atlantic\n", "\n the establishment and growth of European powers in the Atlantic and Pacific\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "What is the most likely explanation for the design of the caravel?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Europeans borrowed the design from Muslim merchants on the North African coast \n", "\n Europeans borrowed the design from North Atlantic traders\n", "\n Italy stole the design from Mediterranean merchants in the 1200s\n", "\n Spanish merchants adopted older forms of ship building from the Portuguese\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "The worst long term effect on the native populations in the Americas of the Columbian Exchange was\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n disease \n", "\n religious change\n", "\n war\n", "\n slavery\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Which branch of Islam is associated with the political/religious title of \u201ccaliphate\u201d?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Sunni \n", "\n Shi\u2019a\n", "\n Protestantism\n", "\n Sufism\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "This European statesman was the leader of the The Berlin Conference:\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n King Leopold II \n", "\n Otto von Bismarck \n", "\n King Louis XIV 6 \n", "\n Henry Stanley \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "All political revolutions between 1750 and 1900 were characterized by \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n the influence of Enlightenment ideals \n", "\n peasants and urban workers refusing to protest \n", "\n eventual choice of universal democracy instead of autocracy \n", "\n the destruction of traditional religion \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "The Opium Trade \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n benefited China by increasing revenue from India \n", "\n led to the Opium Wars which eventually opened up trade in China to English control \n", "\n initially was able to trade out of all Chinese ports \n", "\n opened up the Suez Canal and made Egypt a dominant force in world trade \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "3", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "India: \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n made Britain the preeminent colonial power in the world \n", "\n saw its profits from raw materials sent back to England\n", "\n saw its local businesses threatened by British products \n", "\n all of the above \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "The following were established by European powers in order to send a certain portion of the population to new areas just for the purpose of establishing a new community. \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n penal colonies \n", "\n settler colonies \n", "\n agricultural colonies \n", "\n extended colonies \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "2", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "The Enlightenment helped cause all of the following except: \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The American Revolution \n", "\n The spread of the idea that all men are created equal \n", "\n The spread of authoritarian rule in the 1900s \n", "\n The ideas of the French Revolution \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Which was the final war that Otto von Bismarck waged in his efforts to unify Germany?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Franco-Prussian War \n", "\n The Danish War \n", "\n Austro Prussian War \n", "\n The Polish Revolution \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Which example of imperialism matches the \u201cFly Whisk Incident\u201d? \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n British in Egypt\n", "\n French in Algeria \n", "\n British in China \n", "\n French in Saint-Domingue\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following source to answer the question.\nWe have just ended a century of violence, one possibly more violent than any other in recorded history: world wars and colonial conquests; civil wars, revolutions, and counter revolutions. Although the magnitude of this violence is staggering, it does not astound us.\nThe modern political sensibility sees most political violence as necessary to historical progress. Since the French Revolution, violence has come to be seen as the midwife of history. The French Revolution violence gave us terror, and it gave us a citizens' army. The real secret behind Napoleon's spectacular battlefield success was that his army was not made up of mercenaries but patriots, who killed for a cause, inspired by national sentiment-what we have come to recognize as the civic religion of nationalism. Reflecting on the French Revolution, Hegel wrote that man was willing to die for a cause of greater value to him than life itself. Maybe Hegel should have added: man is also willing to kill for such a cause. This, I think, is truer of our times that it was in the past.\n\nSource: Good Muslim Bad Muslim: America, the Cold War, and the Roots of Terror, Mahmood Mamdani (2004), 3.\n\nWhich of the following is the best representation of the central argument of the above passage? \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The 19th century was likely the most violent century of human history \n", "\n Nationalism is at the root of the extreme violence of the 20th and 21st century \n", "\n Hegel was right about people's beliefs of the French Revolution \n", "\n Napoleon's success was built on national sentiment and patriotism\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "3", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following source to answer the question.\nWe have just ended a century of violence, one possibly more violent than any other in recorded history: world wars and colonial conquests; civil wars, revolutions, and counter revolutions. Although the magnitude of this violence is staggering, it does not astound us.\nThe modern political sensibility sees most political violence as necessary to historical progress. Since the French Revolution, violence has come to be seen as the midwife of history. The French Revolution violence gave us terror, and it gave us a citizens' army. The real secret behind Napoleon's spectacular battlefield success was that his army was not made up of mercenaries but patriots, who killed for a cause, inspired by national sentiment-what we have come to recognize as the civic religion of nationalism. Reflecting on the French Revolution, Hegel wrote that man was willing to die for a cause of greater value to him than life itself. Maybe Hegel should have added: man is also willing to kill for such a cause. This, I think, is truer of our times that it was in the past.\n\nSource: Good Muslim Bad Muslim: America, the Cold War, and the Roots of Terror, Mahmood Mamdani (2004), 3.\n\nWhich historical example could be used to refute the central argument of the above passage? \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The Atlantic Revolutions of the 18th and early 19th centuries \n", "\n Trench warfare of World War One \n", "\n Polish and French resistance movements during World War Two \n", "\n Non-violence movements of the 20th century \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following source to answer the question.\nWe have just ended a century of violence, one possibly more violent than any other in recorded history: world wars and colonial conquests; civil wars, revolutions, and counter revolutions. Although the magnitude of this violence is staggering, it does not astound us.\nThe modern political sensibility sees most political violence as necessary to historical progress. Since the French Revolution, violence has come to be seen as the midwife of history. The French Revolution violence gave us terror, and it gave us a citizens' army. The real secret behind Napoleon's spectacular battlefield success was that his army was not made up of mercenaries but patriots, who killed for a cause, inspired by national sentiment-what we have come to recognize as the civic religion of nationalism. Reflecting on the French Revolution, Hegel wrote that man was willing to die for a cause of greater value to him than life itself. Maybe Hegel should have added: man is also willing to kill for such a cause. This, I think, is truer of our times that it was in the past.\n\nSource: Good Muslim Bad Muslim: America, the Cold War, and the Roots of Terror, Mahmood Mamdani (2004), 3.\n\nWhich piece of immediate historical context is required to understand the passage above \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The end of the Cold War led historians to make new historical arguments about violence \n", "\n Recent terrorist movements and attacks triggered historians to research the concept of violence \n", "\n The establishment of the UN Human Rights Declaration caused historians to re-assess violence of previous periods \n", "\n Growing terrorist organizations caused reactionary movements in Europe\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "3", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following source to answer the question.\nWe have just ended a century of violence, one possibly more violent than any other in recorded history: world wars and colonial conquests; civil wars, revolutions, and counter revolutions. Although the magnitude of this violence is staggering, it does not astound us.\nThe modern political sensibility sees most political violence as necessary to historical progress. Since the French Revolution, violence has come to be seen as the midwife of history. The French Revolution violence gave us terror, and it gave us a citizens' army. The real secret behind Napoleon's spectacular battlefield success was that his army was not made up of mercenaries but patriots, who killed for a cause, inspired by national sentiment-what we have come to recognize as the civic religion of nationalism. Reflecting on the French Revolution, Hegel wrote that man was willing to die for a cause of greater value to him than life itself. Maybe Hegel should have added: man is also willing to kill for such a cause. This, I think, is truer of our times that it was in the past.\n\nSource: Good Muslim Bad Muslim: America, the Cold War, and the Roots of Terror, Mahmood Mamdani (2004), 3.\n\nWhich of the following claims is most aligned with the above passage? \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n People are generally less shocked by violence than they used to be \n", "\n Patriotism always leads to successful military campaigns \n", "\n Nationalism is no longer at the heart of violence in the present day \n", "\n The French Revolution caused the violence we see in the present day \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following primary source to answer the following question.\nGermany in the epoch of the witch hunt was not a unified state, and did not become so until the nineteenth century. It was a patchwork of jurisdictions and political entities of varied size and structure. Obermarchtal, for instance, where Ursula Gotz was accused, was little more than a village, the administrative seat of a minute territory governed by a monastery. Across Germany, ecclesiastical boundaries, areas of legal jurisdiction, lordship and political boundaries rarely coincided, a confusion that left its mark on the witch hunt. A bishop might be a secular ruler of one part of his domain, with full judicial power, but wield only religious authority in other parts of his diocese and lack the power to instigate trials. It is striking that most of the mass persecutions took place in just such territories, lands ruled by Catholic prince-bishops. A town, large or small, might enjoy the status of imperial city, with no overlord other than the Emperor, a judicial island in a network of surrounding territories. A village court might make its own judgements, the village jurors untrained in the science of law but schooled in local tradition.\nWithin Germany, witch hunts followed different patterns. In some areas, one, two or more witches were burnt every few years, a regular if always terrifying occurrence; in others, none were. But in some regions, mass witch hunts of extraordinary ferocity took place where hundreds and even thousands of individuals lost their lives. Under Ferdinand of Bavaria, in the electorate of Cologne (161237), 2,000 people were killed. Witch-hunting encompassed more 'routine cases, each episode terrifying in the demonstration it gave of the power of the Devil to lead people astray, and mass persecutions where the fear of witchcraft scythed its way through an entire society, killing friends, neighbors, and kin.\n\nSource: Lyndal Roper, Witch Craze (2004), 15.\n\nWhich piece of historical context is most directly associated with the passage above? \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Religious tension of the 16th and 17th centuries led to mass hysteria, resulting in increased fears of the Devil \n", "\n Economic turmoil of the 16th century led to commoners to put the blame on common women in German society \n", "\n The reunification of the Protestant and Catholic churches in 1600 led to increased amounts of persecutions who did not support the reunification \n", "\n The discovery of the Americas in the 15th century led to decades of violence and competition between European states, leading to violence between commoners\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following primary source to answer the following question.\nGermany in the epoch of the witch hunt was not a unified state, and did not become so until the nineteenth century. It was a patchwork of jurisdictions and political entities of varied size and structure. Obermarchtal, for instance, where Ursula Gotz was accused, was little more than a village, the administrative seat of a minute territory governed by a monastery. Across Germany, ecclesiastical boundaries, areas of legal jurisdiction, lordship and political boundaries rarely coincided, a confusion that left its mark on the witch hunt. A bishop might be a secular ruler of one part of his domain, with full judicial power, but wield only religious authority in other parts of his diocese and lack the power to instigate trials. It is striking that most of the mass persecutions took place in just such territories, lands ruled by Catholic prince-bishops. A town, large or small, might enjoy the status of imperial city, with no overlord other than the Emperor, a judicial island in a network of surrounding territories. A village court might make its own judgements, the village jurors untrained in the science of law but schooled in local tradition.\nWithin Germany, witch hunts followed different patterns. In some areas, one, two or more witches were burnt every few years, a regular if always terrifying occurrence; in others, none were. But in some regions, mass witch hunts of extraordinary ferocity took place where hundreds and even thousands of individuals lost their lives. Under Ferdinand of Bavaria, in the electorate of Cologne (161237), 2,000 people were killed. Witch-hunting encompassed more 'routine cases, each episode terrifying in the demonstration it gave of the power of the Devil to lead people astray, and mass persecutions where the fear of witchcraft scythed its way through an entire society, killing friends, neighbors, and kin.\n\nSource: Lyndal Roper, Witch Craze (2004), 15.\n\nWhat is the general argument of the first passage? \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Imperial cities enjoyed a number of freedoms other cities or towns did not have \n", "\n Imperial jurisdiction in the Holy Roman Empire was muddled and confusing \n", "\n Witch hunts resulted in the deaths of 10,000 women during the 16th and 17th centuries \n", "\n German unification ended all issues of jurisdiction in Germany\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "2", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following primary source to answer the following question.\nGermany in the epoch of the witch hunt was not a unified state, and did not become so until the nineteenth century. It was a patchwork of jurisdictions and political entities of varied size and structure. Obermarchtal, for instance, where Ursula Gotz was accused, was little more than a village, the administrative seat of a minute territory governed by a monastery. Across Germany, ecclesiastical boundaries, areas of legal jurisdiction, lordship and political boundaries rarely coincided, a confusion that left its mark on the witch hunt. A bishop might be a secular ruler of one part of his domain, with full judicial power, but wield only religious authority in other parts of his diocese and lack the power to instigate trials. It is striking that most of the mass persecutions took place in just such territories, lands ruled by Catholic prince-bishops. A town, large or small, might enjoy the status of imperial city, with no overlord other than the Emperor, a judicial island in a network of surrounding territories. A village court might make its own judgements, the village jurors untrained in the science of law but schooled in local tradition.\nWithin Germany, witch hunts followed different patterns. In some areas, one, two or more witches were burnt every few years, a regular if always terrifying occurrence; in others, none were. But in some regions, mass witch hunts of extraordinary ferocity took place where hundreds and even thousands of individuals lost their lives. Under Ferdinand of Bavaria, in the electorate of Cologne (161237), 2,000 people were killed. Witch-hunting encompassed more 'routine cases, each episode terrifying in the demonstration it gave of the power of the Devil to lead people astray, and mass persecutions where the fear of witchcraft scythed its way through an entire society, killing friends, neighbors, and kin.\n\nSource: Lyndal Roper, Witch Craze (2004), 15.\n\nThe last sentence of the passage implies all the following except? \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Europeans associated witchcraft with the Devil\n", "\n Europeans believed the Devil personally influenced the lives of Europeans\n", "\n Europeans found witch trials to be a perfect opportunity to enact revenge upon their neighbors \n", "\n Even though the targets of the trials were women, no one in society was left untouched by a witch trial\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "2", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following primary source to answer the following question.\nGermany in the epoch of the witch hunt was not a unified state, and did not become so until the nineteenth century. It was a patchwork of jurisdictions and political entities of varied size and structure. Obermarchtal, for instance, where Ursula Gotz was accused, was little more than a village, the administrative seat of a minute territory governed by a monastery. Across Germany, ecclesiastical boundaries, areas of legal jurisdiction, lordship and political boundaries rarely coincided, a confusion that left its mark on the witch hunt. A bishop might be a secular ruler of one part of his domain, with full judicial power, but wield only religious authority in other parts of his diocese and lack the power to instigate trials. It is striking that most of the mass persecutions took place in just such territories, lands ruled by Catholic prince-bishops. A town, large or small, might enjoy the status of imperial city, with no overlord other than the Emperor, a judicial island in a network of surrounding territories. A village court might make its own judgements, the village jurors untrained in the science of law but schooled in local tradition.\nWithin Germany, witch hunts followed different patterns. In some areas, one, two or more witches were burnt every few years, a regular if always terrifying occurrence; in others, none were. But in some regions, mass witch hunts of extraordinary ferocity took place where hundreds and even thousands of individuals lost their lives. Under Ferdinand of Bavaria, in the electorate of Cologne (161237), 2,000 people were killed. Witch-hunting encompassed more 'routine cases, each episode terrifying in the demonstration it gave of the power of the Devil to lead people astray, and mass persecutions where the fear of witchcraft scythed its way through an entire society, killing friends, neighbors, and kin.\n\nSource: Lyndal Roper, Witch Craze (2004), 15.\n\n\"It is striking that most of the mass persecutions took place in just such territories, lands ruled by Catholic prince-bishops.\"\nThe above sentence implies which of the following: \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Catholics ruled more territories in the Holy Roman Empire than Protestants \n", "\n Catholics ruled over territories with clear jurisdiction, while Protestants did not \n", "\n Catholic rulers were more commonly involved with witch-hunt trials than Protestants \n", "\n Protestant churches were untouched by the witch craze\n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "2", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following document to answer the question. \nThe American Civil War is, for the American imagination, the great single event of our history. Without too much wrenching, it may, in fact, be said to be American history. Before the Civil War we had no history in the deepest and most inward sense. There was, of course, the noble vision of the Founding Fathers articulated in the Declaration and the Constitution-the dream of freedom incarnated in a more perfect union.But the Revolution did not create a nation except on paper; and too often in the following years the vision of the Founding Fathers, which men had suffered and died to validate, became merely a daydream of easy and automatic victories, a vulgar delusion of manifest destiny, a conviction of being a people divinely chosen to live on milk and honey at small expense. \nThe vision had not been finally submitted to the test of history. There was little awareness of the cost of having a history. The anguished scrutiny of the meaning of the vision in experience had not become a national reality. It became a reality, and we became a nation, only with the Civil War. \n\nSource: Robert Penn Warren, The Legacy of the Civil War (1961), 3-4.\n\nThe passage above seems to downplay which of the following processes or events? \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The importance of growing nationalism around the world \n", "\n The importance of Enlightenment thinkers of the 19th century \n", "\n The importance of early Manifest Destiny in creating a national identity \n", "\n The importance of history as a changing process \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "2", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following document to answer the question. \nThe American Civil War is, for the American imagination, the great single event of our history. Without too much wrenching, it may, in fact, be said to be American history. Before the Civil War we had no history in the deepest and most inward sense. There was, of course, the noble vision of the Founding Fathers articulated in the Declaration and the Constitution-the dream of freedom incarnated in a more perfect union.But the Revolution did not create a nation except on paper; and too often in the following years the vision of the Founding Fathers, which men had suffered and died to validate, became merely a daydream of easy and automatic victories, a vulgar delusion of manifest destiny, a conviction of being a people divinely chosen to live on milk and honey at small expense. \nThe vision had not been finally submitted to the test of history. There was little awareness of the cost of having a history. The anguished scrutiny of the meaning of the vision in experience had not become a national reality. It became a reality, and we became a nation, only with the Civil War. \n\nSource: Robert Penn Warren, The Legacy of the Civil War (1961), 3-4.\n\nWhat piece of historical context would best explain the central topic and research of the above passage? \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n The intense rivalry of the Cold War made historians refocus on The United States' democratic past \n", "\n The years after the end of World War Two made historians look at the history of nationalism in various countries \n", "\n The centennial anniversary of the Civil War caused historians to reassess the meaning of the Civil War, for American history \n", "\n The assassination of John F. Kennedy caused historians to publish works that aimed to create a unified national identity \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "0", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following document to answer the question. \nThe American Civil War is, for the American imagination, the great single event of our history. Without too much wrenching, it may, in fact, be said to be American history. Before the Civil War we had no history in the deepest and most inward sense. There was, of course, the noble vision of the Founding Fathers articulated in the Declaration and the Constitution-the dream of freedom incarnated in a more perfect union.But the Revolution did not create a nation except on paper; and too often in the following years the vision of the Founding Fathers, which men had suffered and died to validate, became merely a daydream of easy and automatic victories, a vulgar delusion of manifest destiny, a conviction of being a people divinely chosen to live on milk and honey at small expense. \nThe vision had not been finally submitted to the test of history. There was little awareness of the cost of having a history. The anguished scrutiny of the meaning of the vision in experience had not become a national reality. It became a reality, and we became a nation, only with the Civil War. \n\nSource: Robert Penn Warren, The Legacy of the Civil War (1961), 3-4.\n\nWhat is the central argument of the above passage?\n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n An American \"nation\" was created during and after the Civil War \n", "\n The Founding Fathers were not that important in creating a national identity in the United States \n", "\n The American Revolution created a true American nation that was challenged by the American Civil War \n", "\n Manifest destiny was at the center of creating a national identity in the United States \n"]}, {"points": "1", "Answer": "1", "correct_ans_explanation": "", "wrong_ans_explanation": "", "question": "Use the following document to answer the question. \nThe American Civil War is, for the American imagination, the great single event of our history. Without too much wrenching, it may, in fact, be said to be American history. Before the Civil War we had no history in the deepest and most inward sense. There was, of course, the noble vision of the Founding Fathers articulated in the Declaration and the Constitution-the dream of freedom incarnated in a more perfect union.But the Revolution did not create a nation except on paper; and too often in the following years the vision of the Founding Fathers, which men had suffered and died to validate, became merely a daydream of easy and automatic victories, a vulgar delusion of manifest destiny, a conviction of being a people divinely chosen to live on milk and honey at small expense. \nThe vision had not been finally submitted to the test of history. There was little awareness of the cost of having a history. The anguished scrutiny of the meaning of the vision in experience had not become a national reality. It became a reality, and we became a nation, only with the Civil War. \n\nSource: Robert Penn Warren, The Legacy of the Civil War (1961), 3-4.\n\nThe ideas in the above passage are most similar to which of the following? \n", "negative_points": "0", "duration_in_seconds": "60", "question_type": "1", "options": ["\n Enlightenment ideas expressed by thinkers such as John Locke and Jean-Jacques Rousseau \n", "\n Bismarck's ideas of unifying Germany as one nation-state \n", "\n The British colonization of Western Africa as a critical moment in British history \n", "\n The ideas expressed in the French Revolution \n"]}]}